Guide to the Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
21-37-2227
Cornell University Media Services Photo Section
20 cubic ft.; four filing cabinets.
Photographs, negatives, subject cards
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Extension Bulletins with photographs annotated to give Media Services negative numbers. Also photographs of New York State Fair and Farm and Home Week exhibits. File cabinets with negative files and card files by subject.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Extension Bulletins with photographs annotated to give Media Services negative numbers. Also photographs of New York State Fair and Farm and Home Week exhibits. File cabinets with negative files and card files by subject.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Description--Views.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.; New York State College of Human Ecology.
Subjects:
Agriculture--Study and teaching
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Negatives.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Subject Cards and Negatives
  2 filing cabinets containing 4x5 and smaller negatives and 60 card boxes (Boxes 39-98) of corresponding file cards containing subject, thumbnail photograph, date and negative number. Negatives in chronological (negative #) order. File cards organized by subject. Drawer list available.
  - Subject File Cards
    - Aerial Photos, FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
    - Archives, FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
    - Astronomy, FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
    - Ag Leaders' Forum, FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
      - Conservation Leaders' Forum 1969, FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
      - Ag Leaders' Forum 1970, FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
    - Ag Progress Days (Farm & Home Week), FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
      - 1948, FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
      - 1949, FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
      - 1950, FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
      - 1951, FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
      - 1952, FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
      - 1953, FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
      - 1954, FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
      - 1955, FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
      - 1956, FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
      - 1957, FC-1- D-1 (Box 39)
      - 1958, FC-1- D-1 (Box 40)
    - Beef Cattle, FC-1- D-1 (Box 40)
      - Feeding, FC-1- D-1 (Box 40)
      - Barn, FC-1- D-1 (Box 40)
      - Field, FC-1- D-1 (Box 40)
      - Fitting & Showing, FC-1- D-1 (Box 40)
      - Research, FC-1- D-1 (Box 40)
      - Misc., FC-1- D-1 (Box 40)
    - Bio-technology, FC-1- D-1 (Box 41)
      - Biotech/Lab Scenes, FC-1- D-1 (Box 41)
      - Resident Teaching, FC-1- D-1 (Box 41)
    - Botany, FC-1- D-1 (Box 41)
      - Coffee, FC-1- D-1 (Box 41)
    - Floriculture (or Botany), FC-1- D-1 (Box 41)
      - BTI/Research (Boyce Thompson Institute), FC-1- D-1 (Box 41)
    - Cities, Towns, Villages, Homes, FC-1- D-1 (Box 41)
      - Ithaca and Vicinity, FC-1- D-1 (Box 41)
        - Street Scenes, FC-1- D-1 (Box 41)
      - Housing, FC-1- D-1 (Box 41)
      - Public Buildings, FC-1- D-1 (Box 41)
    - Communications, FC-1- D-2 (Box 41)
      - Art Studio, FC-1- D-2 (Box 41)
      - Artwork - General, FC-1- D-2 (Box 41)
      - Artwork - Lineart, FC-1- D-2 (Box 41-42)
      - Heirloom Vegetable. Garden, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
      - Artwork - Mounting, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
      - Artwork - Photograms, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
      - Artwork - Plants, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
      - Slide Sets, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
      - Credit-Line " End", FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
      - Layout, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
      - Letterheads, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
      - Ozalids, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
      - Posters, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
      - Seals and Symbols General, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
        - Agriculture College, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
        - Extension, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
        - 4H, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
        - HE, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
        - Obsolete, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
      - Signs, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
      - Silk Screening, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42)
      - Bulletins, FC-1- D-2 (Box 42-43)
        - ALS News, FC-1- D-2 (Box 43)
        - Cornell Rec., FC-1- D-2 (Box 43)
        - ETI Bulletin, FC-1- D-2 (Box 43)
        - F & LSQ (Food and Life Science Quarterly), FC-1- D-2 (Box 43)
        - Green Acres, FC-1- D-2 (Box 43)
        - H.E. Forum, FC-1- D-2 (Box 43)
        - H.E. News, FC-1- D-2 (Box 43)
        - I.A. Newsle, FC-1- D-2 (Box 43)
        - AAACE, FC-1- D-2 (Box 43)
        - Distribution, FC-1- D-2 (Box 43)
        - Illustration, FC-1- D-2 (Box 43)
        - Preparation, FC-1- D-2 (Box 43)
      - SS/Negatives, FC-1- D-2 (Box 43)
      - Vision, FC-1- D-2 (Box 44)
      - Communication Training, FC-1- D-2 (Box 44)
        - Computers, FC-1- D-2 (Box 44)
        - County News Service, FC-1- D-2 (Box 44)
      - Extension Teaching and Information, FC-1- D-2 (Box 44)
      - Graduate Program, FC-1- D-2 (Box 44)
      - Photographs, FC-1- D-2 (Box 44)
      - Radio, FC-1- D-2 (Box 44)
      - Resident Teaching, FC-1- D-2 (Box 44)
      - Rural School Leaflets, FC-1- D-2 (Box 44)
      - Special Service (Science at Work), FC-1- D-2 (Box 44)
      - Special Presentations, FC-1- D-2 (Box 44)
        - NY Dynamics Agriculture Series, FC-1- D-2 (Box 45)
        - Books/Presentations, FC-1- D-2 (Box 45)
        - Agway Book-Animal Hus., FC-1- D-2 (Box 45)
        - GLF - Eastern States Pres., FC-1- D-2 (Box 45)
        - Waste Disposal Book, FC-1- D-2 (Box 45)
        - Home Economics Council Pub., FC-1- D-2 (Box 45)
        - R.R.D. Book 1964, FC-1- D-2 (Box 45)
        - Sugar Book, FC-1- D-2 (Box 45)
      - Television, FC-1- D-3 (Box 45)
        - ETV, FC-1- D-3 (Box 45)
        - Scenes taken by TV film CTR, FC-1- D-3 (Box 45)
      - Visual Aids, FC-1- D-3 (Box 45)
        - Department Activities, FC-1- D-3 (Box 45)
        - Equipment, FC-1- D-3 (Box 46)
        - Use, FC-1- D-3 (Box 46)
    - Cornell University, FC-1- D-3 (Box 46)
      - Activities, FC-1- D-3 (Box 46)
        - Awards, FC-1- D-3 (Box 46)
        - College Fund, FC-1- D-3 (Box 46)
        - Conferences, FC-1- D-3 (Box 46)
        - Commencement, FC-1- D-3 (Box 47)
        - Dedication Ceremonies, FC-1- D-3 (Box 47)
        - Presentations, FC-1- D-3 (Box 47)
        - Plaques, FC-1- D-3 (Box 47)
        - Receptions, FC-1- D-3 (Box 47)
        - Retirement Ceremonies, FC-1- D-3
        - Student Activities, FC-1- D-3 (Box 47)
      - Buildings, FC-1- D-3 (Box 47)
        - Academic I, FC-1- D-3 (Box 47)
        - Bailey Hall, FC-1- D-3 (Box 47)
        - Agronomy Buildings, FC-1- D-3 (Box 47)
        - BTI (Boyce Thompson Institute), FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Caldwell Hall, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Clock Tower, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Comstock Hall, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - New Comstock Hall, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Harford T & R Research Center, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Kenneth Post Lab, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Law School, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Malott Hall, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Mann Library, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - MVR, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Morrison Hall, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Plant Science, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Poultry Disease Lab, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Riley-Robb Hall, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Roberts Hall, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - C/A Exhibit and Art Studio, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Savage Hall, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Statler Hall, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Stocking Hall, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Stone Hall, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Thurston Hall, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Vet. College, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Vet. College Lab Scenes, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Warren Hall, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
        - Biotechnology, FC-1- D-3 (Box 48)
      - Campus Scenes, FC-1- D-3 (Box 49)
      - Resident Teaching (Agriculture College), FC-1- D-4 (Box 49)
        - Foreign Students, FC-1- D-4 (Box 49)
        - Farm Practice, FC-1- D-4 (Box 49)
        - Graduates (Careers), FC-1- D-4 (Box 49)
        - Graduate Students, FC-1- D-4 (Box 49)
        - Lab Scenes - Field Trips, FC-1- D-4 (Box 50)
        - Scholarship, FC-1- D-4 (Box 50)
        - Student Housing, FC-1- D-4 (Box 50)
    - Dairy Cattle, FC-1- D-4 (Box 50)
      - Artificial Insemination, FC-1- D-4 (Box 50)
      - Bulls, FC-1- D-4 (Box 50)
      - Calves, FC-1- D-4 (Box 50)
      - Conformation, FC-1- D-4 (Box 50)
      - Dairy Herd Improvement, FC-1- D-4 (Box 50)
      - Dehorning, FC-1- D-4 (Box 50)
      - Disease Control, FC-1- D-4 (Box 50)
      - Husbandry, FC-1- D-4 (Box 50)
      - Feeding, FC-1- D-4 (Box 50)
      - Field, FC-1- D-4 (Box 50-51)
      - Milking, FC-1- D-4 (Box 51)
      - Fitting - Showing, FC-1- D-4 (Box 51)
      - Research, FC-1- D-4 (Box 51)
      - Facilities, FC-1- D-4 (Box 51)
      - Growth - Development, FC-1- D-4 (Box 51)
    - Dairy Products, FC-1- D-4 (Box 51)
      - Butter & Buttermilk, FC-1- D-4 (Box 51)
      - Cheese, FC-1- D-4 (Box 51)
      - Ice Cream, FC-1- D-4 (Box 51)
      - Milk, FC-1- D-4 (Box 51)
      - Research, FC-1- D-4 (Box 51-52)
      - Nutrition, FC-1- D-4 (Box 52)
    - Damage, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
      - Flood, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
      - Frost, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
      - Ice, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
      - Pollution, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
    - Economics, Management, Marketing, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
      - Home Study, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
      - Farm Business, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
      - Labor Saving, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
      - Farm Labor, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
      - Auctions, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
      - Marketing, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
        - Eggs, Poultry, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
        - Flowers, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
        - Fruit, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
        - General, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
        - Milk, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
        - NY Met. Marketing Office, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
    - Education, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
      - Public Schools, FC-1- D-5 (Box 53)
      - Vocational Agriculture, FC-1- D-5 (Box 54)
      - Agriculture Science Youth Program 1964, FC-1- D-5 (Box 54)
    - Electrification, FC-1- D-5 (Box 54)
      - Wiring, FC-1- D-5 (Box 54)
      - Energy Conservation, FC-1- D-5 (Box 54)
    - Engineering, FC-1- D-5 (Box 54)
      - Engineering Research, FC-1- D-5 (Box 54)
      - Highways, FC-1- D-5 (Box 54)
    - Entomology (Insects), FC-1- D-5 (Box 54)
      - Bees, FC-1- D-5 (Box 54)
        - Honey, FC-1- D-5 (Box 54)
      - Control (Spray-Dust), FC-1- D-5 (Box 54)
      - Damage by Insects, FC-1- D-5 (Box 54)
      - Research, FC-1- D-5 (Box 54)
      - Species, FC-1- D-5 (Box 54)
        - Alfalfa Weevil, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Aphids, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Army Worm, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Beetles, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Cabbage Looper, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Cabbage Maggot, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Cabbage Worm, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Chaffer, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Corn Borer and Earthworm, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Cottony Peach Scale, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Curculio, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Cutworm, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Dogwood Borer, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Elm Bark and Leaf Beetle, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - European Apple Sawfly, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Flies, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Gypsy Moths, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Housefly, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Household Insects, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Juniper Scale, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Leaf Hopper, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Leaf Miner, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Leaf Roller, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Locusts, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Mosquitoes, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Nematode, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Onion Maggot, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Pear Psylla, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Red Mite, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Slugs and Snails, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Squash Bug and Vine Borer, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Tarnish Plant Bug, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Termites, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Thrips, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Tomato Worm, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - Weevils - Carrot, Clover, Pea, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
        - White Grub, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
    - Environment, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
      - Waste Disposal, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
    - Exhibits and Demonstrations, FC-1- D-5 (Box 55)
      - Misc. Exhibits, FC-1- D-5 (Box 56)
      - Models, FC-1- D-5 (Box 56)
    - Farms, FC-1- D-6 (Box 56)
      - Farm Buildings, FC-1- D-6 (Box 56)
      - Barns, FC-1- D-6 (Box 56)
      - Barnyards, Pole, FC-1- D-6 (Box 56)
      - Equipment, FC-1- D-6 (Box 56)
      - Milkhouses, FC-1- D-6 (Box 56)
      - Milking Parlors, FC-1- D-6 (Box 56)
      - Stalls, FC-1- D-6 (Box 56)
      - Ventilation, FC-1- D-6 (Box 56)
      - Farmhouses, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
      - Silos, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
      - Trench, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
      - Upright, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
      - Farm Ponds, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
      - Farm Scenes, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
      - Farm Families, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
      - Farm Waste Disposal, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
    - Fencing, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
    - Field Crops, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
      - Alfalfa, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
      - Birdsfoot Treefoil, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
      - Barley, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
      - Brome Grass, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
      - Clovers, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
      - Corn, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
      - Corn Harvesting, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
      - Grass Silage, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
      - Hay, FC-1- D-6 (Box 57)
        - Driers, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
        - Haying Operations, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
        - Misc. Varieties, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Oats, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Pastures, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Rye, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Seeds, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Sudan Grass, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Sugar Beets, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Timothy, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Wheat, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Waste Water Treatment, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
    - Filing Systems, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
    - Floriculture, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Alliums, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Arrangements, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Christmas, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Dried Flowers, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Funeral, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Corsages, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Cut Flowers, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Damage - Injury, FC-1- D-6 (Box 58)
      - Florists Equipment, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
      - Greenhouses, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
      - Ground Cover, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
      - Hedges, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
      - Herbs, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
      - House Plants, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
      - Research, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
      - Equipment, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
      - Resident Teaching, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
      - Rooting, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
      - Shrubs, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
      - Trees, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
      - Varieties, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
        - Begonia, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
        - Carnations, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
        - Chrysanthemem, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
        - Dogwood, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
        - Gardenia, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
        - Geranium, FC-1- D-6 (Box 59)
        - Hydrangea, FC-1- D-6 (Box 60)
        - Kalanchoe, FC-1- D-6 (Box 60)
        - Lilies, FC-1- D-6 (Box 60)
        - Misc., FC-1- D-6 (Box 60)
        - Orchid, FC-1- D-6 (Box 60)
        - Poinsettias, FC-1- D-6 (Box 60)
        - Roses, FC-1- D-6 (Box 60)
        - Snapdragons, FC-1- D-6 (Box 60)
    - Forestry, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
      - Christmas Trees, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
      - Equipment, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
      - Forests, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
      - Management, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
      - Maple Products, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
      - Trees, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
        - Elms, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
        - Pruning, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
      - Transplanting, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
      - Windbreaks, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
      - Wood Preservation, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
      - Wood Products, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
    - Geneva Experiment Station, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
      - Seed Analysis, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
    - Goats, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
    - Foreign Visitors (?), FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
    - Historical, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
      - Buildings, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60)
        - Roberts Hall, FC-1- D-7 (Box 60-61)
        - Stone Hall, FC-1- D-7 (Box 61)
        - Fernow Hall, FC-1- D-7 (Box 61)
      - Clinton House Historical, FC-1- D-7 (Box 61)
      - Entomology, FC-1- D-7 (Box 61)
      - Extension Service, FC-1- D-7 (Box 61)
      - Horticulture Exhibit, Rochester, NY, FC-1- D-7 (Box 61)
      - Exhibits, FC-1- D-7 (Box 61)
      - Farm Animals, FC-1- D-7 (Box 61)
      - Indians, FC-1- D-7 (Box 61)
      - Misc., FC-1- D-7 (Box 61)
      - Equipment, Machinery, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
      - Farm Labor, World War II, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
      - Farmer's Museum, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
      - Field Harvesting and Marketing, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
      - Flood Droughts, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
      - Musical Instruments, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
      - Reports, Signs, Newspaper Clippings, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
      - Scenery, Landscapes, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
      - People, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
      - 75th Anniversary, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
      - Historical/Cornell Faculty, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
      - Historical/People Unknown, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
      - Historical Groups, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
      - Historical Unknown People, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
      - Historical - Posters, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
    - Horses, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
      - 4-H Program, FC-1- D-7 (Box 62)
    - Industry, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - International Agriculture Development, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Philippines - Los Banyos, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
    - Irrigation, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
    - Lakes and Streams, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
    - Landscaping, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
    - Lawns and Ground Cover, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
    - Machinery, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Balers, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Buck Rakes, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Combines, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Conveyors - Distributors, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Corn Elevator, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Corn Picker, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Cultivator, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Elevators (Grain and Hay), FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Ensilage Cutter, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Field Chopper, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Harvesters, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Hay Blowers, Driers, Loaders, Rakes, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Homemade Machinery, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Lime Spreader, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Mowers, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Planters- Drills, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Plows, FC-1- D-7 (Box 63)
      - Plow Models, FC-1- D-7? (Box 64)
      - Potato Diggers, FC-1- D-7 (Box 64)
      - Power Shovel, FC-1- D-7 (Box 64)
      - Pumps, FC-1- D-7 (Box 64)
      - Refrigeration, FC-1- D-7 (Box 64)
      - Sprayers, FC-1- D-7 (Box 64)
      - Testing Equipment, FC-1- D-7 (Box 64)
      - Threshing Machine, FC-1- D-7 (Box 64)
      - Tractors, FC-1- D-7 (Box 64)
      - Unloaders, FC-1- D-7 (Box 64)
      - Weed Burners, FC-1- D-7 (Box 64)
    - Maps, FC-1- D-7 (Box 64)
      - New York State, FC-1- D-7 (Box 64)
      - (Ag. Research Aerial Views), FC-1- D-7 (Box 64)
      - Counties, FC-1- D-7 (Box 64)
      - USA and other states, FC-1- D-7 (Box 64)
    - Meats, FC-1- D-8 (Box 64)
      - Beef, FC-1- D-8 (Box 64)
      - Meats Variety, FC-1- D-8 (Box 64)
      - Research, FC-1- D-8 (Box 64)
        - Research - Fat Determination, FC-1- D-8 (Box 64-66)
      - Beef, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
      - Lamb, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
      - Meat Handling, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
      - Equipment, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
      - Freezing, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
      - Kosher Butchering, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
      - Pork, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
      - Bulletin 732, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
      - Veal, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
    - Music, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
    - Natural Resources, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
      - Research, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
    - Organizations, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
      - Alumni Association, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
      - Community Chest, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
      - Cornell Ext. Club, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
        - County Ag Agents Association, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
        - County Ext. Buildings, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
        - Extension Service, FC-1- D-8 (Box 66)
        - County Ag. Agents at Work, FC-1- D-8 (Box 67)
        - Demonstrations, FC-1- D-8 (Box 67)
        - Field Days, FC-1- D-8 (Box 67)
        - Urban Gardening, FC-1- D-8 (Box 67)
        - Plowing Contest, FC-1- D-8 (Box 67)
      - State Ext. Advisory Council, FC-1- D-8 (Box 67)
        - Tours, FC-1- D-8 (Box 67)
      - 4-H, FC-1- D-8 (Box 67)
        - Bicycle Project, FC-1- D-8 (Box 67)
        - Camp, FC-1- D-8 (Box 67)
        - Conservation, FC-1- D-8 (Box 68)
        - Leader Training, FC-1- D-8 (Box 68)
        - Misc., FC-1- D-8 (Box 68)
        - Youth Development, FC-1- D-8 (Box 68)
        - Club Congress, FC-1- D-8 (Box 68)
        - Demonstrations, FC-1- D-8 (Box 68)
        - Fitting and Showing Contest, FC-1- D-8 (Box 68)
          - I.F.Y.E., FC-1- D-8 (Box 68)
          - Judging Teams, FC-1- D-8 (Box 68)
          - Horse Show, FC-1- D-8 (Box 68)
          - Judge Training, FC-1- D-8 (Box 68)
        - Projects, FC-1- D-8 (Box 68)
        - Contests, FC-1- D-8 (Box 68)
        - 4-H Agents Association, FC-1- D-8 (Box 68)
        - Home Demonstration Agents Association, FC-1- D-8 (Box 68)
    - People, FC-2- D-9 (Box 68-69)
      - Faculty Groups, FC-2- D-9 (Box 69)
      - Groups General, FC-2- D-9 (Box 69)
      - Foreign Visitors, FC-2- D-9 (Box 69)
      - Portraits, FC-2- D-9 (Box 69)
        - A-G, FC-2- D-9 (Box 69)
        - H-Y, FC-2- D-9 (Box 70)
        - Z, FC-2- D-9 (Box 71)
      - Paintings, FC-2- D-9 (Box 71)
      - Typical Farmers, FC-2- D-9 (Box 71)
    - Plant Breeding, FC-2- D-9 (Box 71)
    - Plant Pathology, FC-2- D-9 (Box 71)
    - Pomology, FC-2- D-9 (Box 71)
      - Research, FC-2- D-9 (Box 71)
      - Varieties, FC-2- D-9 (Box 71)
        - Apples, FC-2- D-9 (Box 71)
          - Budding, FC-2- D-9 (Box 71)
          - Chemical Thinning, FC-2- D-9 (Box 71)
          - Harvesting, FC-2- D-9 (Box 71)
          - Injury, FC-2- D-9 (Box 71)
          - Pruning, FC-2- D-9 (Box 71)
          - Insect Damage, FC-2- D-9 (Box 71)
          - Storage, FC-2- D-9 (Box 71)
          - Waxing, FC-2- D-9 (Box 72)
        - Berries Misc., FC-2- D-9 (Box 72)
        - Blueberries, FC-2- D-9 (Box 72)
        - Cherries, FC-2- D-9 (Box 72)
        - Grapes, FC-2- D-9 (Box 72)
        - Peaches, FC-2- D-9 (Box 72)
        - Pears, FC-2- D-9 (Box 72)
        - Raspberries, FC-2- D-9 (Box 72)
        - Strawberries, FC-2- D-9 (Box 72)
    - Older Portraits, FC-2- D-10 (Box 72)
      - A-C, FC-2- D-10 (Box 72)
      - C-J, FC-2- D-10 (Box 73)
      - K-P, FC-2- D-10 (Box 74)
      - P-W, FC-2- D-10 (Box 75)
      - W-Z, FC-2- D-10 (Box 76)
    - Poultry, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
      - Barbecue (Scenes), FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
      - Equipment, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
      - Preparation, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
      - Breeds, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
        - Laying Tests, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
      - Breeding, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
      - Brooding, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
        - Permanent, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
        - Coal, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
        - Electric, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
        - Radiant, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
        - Range, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
      - Caponizing, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
      - Culling, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
      - De-Beaking, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
      - Disease and Parasites, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
      - Dressing, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
        - Canning, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
        - Freezing, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
        - Frying, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
        - Roasting, FC-2- D-11 (Box 76)
        - Stewing, FC-2- D-11 (Box 77)
      - Chicken, FC-2- D-11 (Box 77)
      - Ducks, FC-2- D-11 (Box 77)
      - Eggs, FC-2- D-11 (Box 77)
        - Eggroom, FC-2- D-11 (Box 77)
        - Equipment, FC-2- D-11 (Box 77)
        - Feeding, FC-2- D-11 (Box 77)